Okay, let's actually put our item on the
screen now because
that's what we want to do. That's the
whole reason we created the element. So,
in order to do that, we have now set
we've created the element and we've set
its text content. Now, all we need to do
is add it to the screen. The way you add
it to the screen um is you have to find
the spot you want to add it to. So, I'm
going to say document
query selector and I am going to look
for this output ul. So, I'm going to
look for something that has the ID of
output.
And then I'm going to say append child.
What this does is it takes in an element
and it appends it to the screen. So,
we're going to take in this element and
we're going to append it to the screen.
So, I'm going to access that element.
And now I'm going to save this. So,
let's come over to our running thing and
we're going to say go shopping.
And now go shopping has been added to
the screen. Let's try and do our button
trick again. button on click
alert one. Close the button. Hi.
And if we add it, you'll notice it
turned it into text content and put it
on the screen. So, the cross-ite
scripting attack no longer worked
because we're not directly setting inner
HTML, which means they can't give us
HTML. We're setting the text content,
but we are still creating an element.
And in this way, we were safely able to
sanitize and put it on the screen.